<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experience on</title><link>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4th Job</title><link>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-work-as-a-freelance">My work as a freelance&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As a freelancer, I worked on two major projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Project #1: an innovative real-time reverb-canceling embedded system for speaker correction using deep learning and reinforcement learning. In this project I did the full system design on STM32H7, from concept to prototype. It included a Qualcomm QCC chip for top-quality Bluetooth audio. Most development focused on building fast DSP algorithms for the ARM microcontroller and pushing performance to the limit for large convolutions. At the same time, I programmed a CNN in Python with TensorFlow for other tasks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3rd Job</title><link>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-3/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="firmware-engineer">Firmware Engineer&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As a Firmware Engineer, I worked with STM32 and ESP32 to develop and maintain firmware for consumer electronics. Part of my job was to develop a system for mass-programming custom PCBs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>All the projects I worked on focused on cost optimization, so the microcontrollers had very limited resources. For that reason, I used low-level APIs and bare-metal programming for STM32, and FreeRTOS for ESP32.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>2nd Job</title><link>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="signal-processing-and-rd-engineer">Signal Processing and R&amp;amp;D Engineer&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>During my time at Zigor I had an important role as the main signal processing engineer and PCB designer in the development of various power converters and power electronic devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was in charge of the hardware development of a power supply with over 10 kV insulation barriers, where I designed essential parts like analog and EMI filters, and implemented digital filters in the microcontroller. I also led the whole PCB design validation and testing using Altium.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>1st Job</title><link>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://javiergarciaserrano.com/experience/job-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="rd-scholarship-embedded-software">R&amp;amp;D Scholarship, Embedded Software&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>As a Junior Intern at the Universitat Politècnica de València, I had the chance to work on different projects that helped me build my technical and professional skills. Working with experienced engineers and PhDs, I contributed to the development of research devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During the internship, I was asked to write firmware in C for communicating several Texas Instruments microcontrollers over a single serial line. I also did extensive research on minimizing transistor losses in power converters and worked on industrial Windows software development.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>